

ASSOCIATE POWER BI DEVELOPER

Summary -

Professional Power BI Developer with two years of experience in data discovery, reporting, and development. Strong creative and analytical skills who is always looking for ways to gain competencies and strengthen abilities.



jasmineking0301@gmail.com



JasmineKing19.github.io

Skills

- Microsoft Power Platform
- Microsoft Office Suite
- SQL
- Tableau
- R/R-Studio
- Python/Java/C++
- Data Discovery/Analysis
- Strong Communication
- Engaged Team Player

Education

M.S. - DATA SCIENCE & ANALYTICS

Old Dominion University 2023 - PRESENT

B.S.B.A. - MANAGEMENT

Christopher Newport University

2019 - 2023

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Douglas Anderson School of the Arts 2016-2019

Experience

ASSOCIATE POWER BI DEVELOPER

Ferguson Enterprises

January 2023 - Present

- Data discovery, querying, and analysis
- Build back-end reporting logic and front-end reporting interface for dashboards and reports
- Present data visualizations and analysis to stakeholders
- Automate manual reporting cadence using Power Platform or improved SQL

PROJECT MANAGEMENT & DASHBOARD DEVELOPER INTERN

National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA)

February 2022 - January 2023

- Implemented modernization of work methods and digital tools using Microsoft O365 Platform
- Built project management training program application using Power Platform and Python
- Educated stakeholders on Power Platform and Python tools

OPERATIONS RESEARCH ANALYST INTERN

Cybersecurity & Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA)

June 2022 - September 2022

- Data discovery and analysis
- Created and presented workforce analytics reports for stakeholders
- Participated in workforce planning strategy meetings and educated coworkers on ways to automate processes